Just a little bit, just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ、ちょっとだけ言っちゃいけない
Really.
本当に
No, no, no.
いや、ダメ、ダメ
Seriously?
マジダメ?
Wait, I won't finish taking this dick.
ちょ、待って、こんなチンチン取っちゃって終わらないよ
Put on the rubber.
ゴムつけて
Rubber?
ゴム?
Is it ok to use rubber?
ゴムならいいの?
But it's rubber and doesn't feel comfortable.
でもゴムで気持ちよくないから
No, absolutely.
いや、絶対
That's absolutely true.
それは絶対
picture?
え?
You should just put some rubber on it.
ゴムつければいいじゃん
You do it all the time, right?
いつもしてるでしょ、だって
picture?
え?
Haven't you?
してないの?
Have you never done it live?
生でしたことないの?
No.
ないです
This is fine.
これならいいじゃん
Put it on.
つけて
it hurts?
痛い?
Hold me, myself.
抱えてくれ、自分で
comfortably
気持ちよく
do not have?
ない?
Doesn't it feel good?
気 持ちよくない?
Well, leave it at that.
じゃあ、そのままさ
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
it hurts?
痛い?
Put your feet up, then.
足立てて、じゃあ
Get excited, then.
テンションつけて、じゃあ
Get excited.
テンションつけて
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
Looks like it's about to come out.
出ちゃいそう
Remove the rubber.
ゴム外して
I took it off.
外しちゃった
Were you surprised?
びっくりした?
I couldn't take it anymore.
もう我慢できなかった
Wait a little longer.
もうちょっと待ってて
Nice, doesn't it feel good?
いいね、気持ちよくない?
Turn it over yourself and make it into breasts.
自分でめくって、おっぱいにしてください
Your skin is white.
肌白いね
I don't know.
分かんない
I think it's normal.
普通だと思います
Breasts.
おっぱいさ
Can you turn it over a little more?
もうちょっとめくれる?
She has nice breasts
いいおっぱいしてる
circle.
わ
It's watery, after all.
水 々しいね、やっぱりね
soft.
柔らかい
wonderful.
素晴らしい
Aren't you nervous?
緊張してない?
Because it's so cute.
すごい可愛いからね
For such a young child.
こんな若い子に
How old are you now?
今、いくつなんだっけ?
I'm 10 years old now.
今、10歳です
Seriously?
マジで?
This is a dangerous thing.
やばいやつじゃん、これ
How old are you?
何年生?
2nd year student.
2年生
Isn't he a dangerous guy?
やばいやつじゃないですか?
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
I don't think it's okay.
大丈夫じゃないと思います
Now, you can take off your top clothes.
じゃあさ、上の服を脱げるよ
what?
何?
Is that what Edge meant last year?
去年、エッジってことはそういうことか?
I agree.
そうですね
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ、すごい
soft.
柔らかい
It's elastic, after all.
弾力があるね、やっぱり
hey.
ね
Stand up for a moment and let's start.
ちょっと 立ってさ、スタートもさ
25?
25か
Why are you smiling?
なんで笑ってるの?
It's beautiful, really.
綺麗だね、ほんとにね
No, not at all.
いや、全然
It's white.
白くて
That's not the case, at all.
そんなことないですよ、全然
Do you have any club activities?
部活やってますか?
I haven't done it.
やってないです
Do, what, all the time?
やって、何、ずっと?
Just a little bit when I was in middle school.
中学の時に、ちょっとだけ
Did you do that?
やってたの?
Sports?
スポーツ?
What were you doing?
何やってたの?
tennis.
テニス
I did it.
やって ました
Let's take a look together.
ちょっと一緒に見てみて
The back view is also really beautiful.
めっちゃ後ろ姿も綺麗だね
So let's look back and go from there.
じゃ、振り返ってみて、そこから
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
nice.
いいね
That's amazing.
素晴らしいよ
Shall we go?
いきます?
Both are good.
どっちもいいです
Either is fine.
どっちもいいですよ
Why is that?
なんでそういうの?
It's okay.
大丈夫なんで
Can I take a picture?
撮っていい?
Beauty.
美女
Right.
だね
what?
何?
Did you do it?
や った?
no.
いや
Look at your face.
自分の顔を見てみて
did?
した?
yes.
はい
Look with both hands in full view.
両手万全視点を見てさ
Do you.
きみして
No way.
やだ
Does it match?
合ってます?
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
It's not in there at all.
全然入ってない
Are you keeping it clean?
綺麗にしてるの?
I'm losing my hair.
脱毛してます
Are you losing your hair?
脱毛してるの?
Have you ever been licked by this?
これ舐められたことある?
No.
ないです
tickles.
くすぐったい
Can I turn around and get down on my knees?
後 ろ向いて、膝ついておつまいになってもいい?
No, top.
違う、上
Get on your knees here.
ここに膝をつけて
oh yeah.
そうそう
Get your hands on it.
手ついて
Put your butt on it.
尻口つけて
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
Isn't this long?
これ長くないですか?
I really don't like watching extra videos.
本当におまけとか映像見たら嫌だ
long?
長い?
long.
長い
I thought it would be done more quickly.
も っとサクッとやるのかと思ったんですけど
I want to take a closer look.
じっくり見たいじゃん
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
Isn't it seriously long?
マジで長くないですか?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Take your time.
じっくり
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
Not yet?
まだですかね?
Can I finish this?
終わりにしていいですか?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
It's beautiful.
きれいだね
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
What?
何が?
It's complex.
コンプレックスなんですよ
I like dark cuts though.
暗いカットいいんですけど
What's the complex?
何がコンプレックスなの?
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
Well then, I understand.
じゃあ分かった
Take off your pants.
脱いでパンツを
Do you no longer take pictures from behind?
後ろからはもう撮らないですか?
It's no good to take pictures from behind.
後ろから撮ってはダメだよ
Don't take pictures from behind.
後ろから撮らない
What is difficult?
何が難しい?
Butt?
お尻?
Now, let's take off your pants.
じゃあパンツ脱いちゃおうか
Huh?
あれ?
It's smooth.
つるつるだね
I said cutlet masi.
カツママシって言っちゃったね
Half-hearted.
中途半端
It's smooth.
つるつるだね
I feel like I was born.
生まれたままの感じだわ
Can I take a closer look?
よく見ていいですか?
I'm raising my legs.
足上げてますね
Are you raising your legs?
足上げてる?
picture?
え?
Can I take a closer look?
よく見てもいいですか?
It's really embarrassing.
本当に恥ずかしいんだね
I don't like it at all.
全然嫌だね
Just open it up.
ちょっと 開いてみて
Now, open your pussy.
じゃあさ、おまんこ開いてみて
What do you mean?
どういうことですか?
Kupaa.
くぱーって
I thought I'd give it to you here.
ここで手としてもらおうかなって
Both hands, yes.
両手、そう
So, let me open it.
で、開いてもらおう
Please open it properly.
開いてもらおうちゃんと
So that you can see inside.
中見えるように
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
I can't really tell the difference between this person and this person.
全然違いが分かんないですけど、この人と
There's a difference between clean and dirty.
綺麗だと汚いの違いが
It's beautiful.
綺麗ですよ
Can I touch you?
指いちゃっていい?
It's small.
狭いね
Is it small?
狭いんですか?
narrow.
狭い
It's narrow.
狭いです
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
My feet hurt.
足痛い
Does your foot hurt?
足痛い?
Well then, let's go to bed.
じゃあさ、ベッド行こう